Guide to the Acacia Fraternity records,1906-2007.
Acacia Fraternity records
- Series X. Brother Membership Files, Brother membership files contain information about each named Acacia fraternity member. Some of the materials include correspondence with the chapter or other brothers, essays written prior to initiation about expectations for the event, and announcements of bir
  - Amon III, William F. (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Anderson, Lester Curtis (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Andrae, William Cook (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Ashley, Wells H (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Baker, Alan L. (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Baker, Robert E. (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Ballard, Horace (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Barnes, Wilbur James (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Barr, Michael (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Bartlett, K. R (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Bates, E. A. (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Baty, James (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Baumgartner, Stephen (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Beaumont, Arthur Bishop (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Bedell, Gordon (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Beischer, William A. (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - Belden, Daniel Stanton (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Bellinger, Harold W. (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Belvin, Kent A. (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Bennett, Chas. Wm. (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - Bennett, Ralph Stamp (Box 12, Folder 38)
  - Benson, Geo. Milton (Box 12, Folder 39)
  - Bent, Clarence F. (Box 12, Folder 40)
  - Berger, Albert I. (Box 12, Folder 41)
  - Bidgood, Carlos French (Box 12, Folder 42)
  - Billig, Thomas Clifford (Box 12, Folder 43)
  - Bills, David (Box 12, Folder 44)
  - Bishop III, Ralph J. (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Bittence, John (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Blume, Louis F. (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Bogan, Samuel D. (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Bolles, Albert Thomas (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Bott, Clarence Comstock (Box 12, Folder 50)
  - Bowman, Ralph (Box 12, Folder 51)
  - Boyles, Arthur F. (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Brackett, Ernest W. (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Bradlee, Thomas (Box 12, Folder 54)
  - Bradley, Jesse Franklin (Box 12, Folder 55)
  - Bradley, Robert Claud (Box 12, Folder 56)
  - Doc (Robert Claud) Bradley Personal Correspondence (Box 12, Folder 57)
  - Brahmer, Leland Frank (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Bridgeman, Bruce (Box 12, Folder 59)
  - Brink, Sheldon E. (Box 12, Folder 60)
  - Brink, Sheldon E. (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Brinton, Chas. Chester (Box 12, Folder 62)
  - Britton, Harry A. (Box 12, Folder 63)
  - Brody, James A. (Box 12, Folder 64)
  - Brown, Kenneth E. (Box 12, Folder 65)
  - Brown, Matthew L. (Box 12, Folder 66)
  - Bunyan, William (Box 12, Folder 67)
  - Burger, Stewart (Box 12, Folder 68)
  - Burnett, Sam. Howard (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Burnett, William C. (Box 12, Folder 70)
  - Burns, Allan F. (Box 12, Folder 71)
  - Burnham, Clifford J. (Box 12, Folder 72)
  - Burton, Frederick C. (Box 12, Folder 73)
  - Cameron, James (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Campbell, Cyril H. (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Campbell, Howard H. (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Canaga, Gordon Byron (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Carter, Wilber Albert (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Caslick, Edward Albert (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Chamberlain, Robert F. (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Chamberlin, Taylor M. (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Cheney, David Wm. (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Cheney, John B. (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Cherry, Richard (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Chrisman, Ross Fremont (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Churchill, Rogers Platt (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Clapp, Roger S. (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Clark, Roy Edwards (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Clark, Roy Ross (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Clarkson, J. M. (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Coffman, John Daniel (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Cole, W. Storrs (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Conlee, George Dyer (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Conroy, Edward A. (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Cormany, Charles E. (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Cosgriff, Ethan (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Cotner, Walter W. (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Cox, Walter E. (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Cragbon, Martin Doyle (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Craig, John (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Crittendon, Charles G. (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Crumb, Stephen E. (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Culbertson, Jason T. (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Curtis, Joseph C. (Box 13, Folder 31)
  - Curtis, Paul P. (Box 13, Folder 32)
  - Cushing, Albert A. (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Cushing, Edward Raymond (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Dallenbach, Karl M. (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Dalrymple, Charles O. (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Daniel, Derril F. (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Darlington, Charles Canby (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Davey, Walter P. (Penn State Chapter) (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Davies, Llewellyn Rhys (Box 13, Folder 40)
  - Davis, Barry G. (Box 13, Folder 41)
  - Davis, Herbert B. (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Deitrich, L. Walter (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Deatrick, Eugene Payton (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - DeCamp, Clayton Earl (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - DeCamp, W. E. (Box 13, Folder 46)
  - DeVolt, Harold Moon (Box 13, Folder 47)
  - Dittmar, Robert W. (Box 13, Folder 48)
  - Dodson, Willard Forest (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Downing, Robert Benjamin (Box 13, Folder 50)
  - du Buisson, Johannes P. (Box 13, Folder 51)
  - Dynes, Oliver Wesley (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Eberhart, Douglas C. (Box 13, Folder 53)
  - Edwards, Llewellyn H. (Box 13, Folder 54)
  - Eisenhut, Peter S. (Box 13, Folder 55)
  - Ellis, Willard Waldo (Box 13, Folder 56)
  - Elmendorf, Richard G. (Box 13, Folder 57)
  - Emerson, Stuart B. (Box 13, Folder 58)
  - Emslie, Charles Maynard (Box 13, Folder 59)
  - Engler, Philip (Box 13, Folder 60)
  - Enos, Everett Emerson (Box 13, Folder 61)
  - Erb, Robert F. (Box 13, Folder 62)
  - Evans, William (Box 13, Folder 63)
  - Farnsworth, James A. (Box 13, Folder 64)
  - Fash, Robert S. (Box 13, Folder 65)
  - Fernschild, Edward Berent (Box 13, Folder 66)
  - Fischell, David (Box 13, Folder 67)
  - Field, Charles H. (Box 13, Folder 68)
  - Fielding, James A. (Box 13, Folder 69)
  - Fish, Donald C. (Box 13, Folder 70)
  - Fisher, John S. (Box 13, Folder 71)
  - Fishman, Steven G. (Box 13, Folder 72)
  - Flegel, Clarence Hubert (Box 13, Folder 73)
  - Fletcher, Corey W. (Box 13, Folder 74)
  - Flickinger, Robert D. (Box 13, Folder 75)
  - Forbes, Allan V. (Box 13, Folder 76)
  - Fox, Bruce R. (Box 13, Folder 77)
  - Fox, Daniel Scott (Box 13, Folder 78)
  - Francis, Edgar W. (Box 13, Folder 79)
  - Franson, Robert T. (Box 13, Folder 80)
  - Frederick, Albert C. (Box 13, Folder 81)
  - Frisbie, John B. (Box 13, Folder 82)
  - Frizzell, Rex R. (Box 13, Folder 83)
  - Fuller, George L. (Box 13, Folder 84)
  - Funk, Horace Clemmer (Box 13, Folder 85)
  - Gaines, Denson (Box 13, Folder 86)
  - Gaines, J. G. (Box 13, Folder 87)
  - Gardner, Hubert Miller (Box 13, Folder 88)
  - Garrelts, J. M. (Box 13, Folder 89)
  - Gibson, William B. (Box 13, Folder 90)
  - Gilbert, Harvey Nicholas (Box 13, Folder 91)
  - Gill, Hermit Herman (Box 13, Folder 92)
  - Gillis, Merl C. (Box 13, Folder 93)
  - Goff, Albert Lewis (Box 13, Folder 94)
  - Godwin, Frederick M. (Box 13, Folder 95)
  - Goldman, Howard "How" (Box 13, Folder 96)
  - Goodman, Lewis Oswald (Box 13, Folder 97)
  - Gorelick, David A. (Box 13, Folder 98)
  - Graves, Michael T. (Box 13, Folder 99)
  - Griest, Richard M. (Box 13, Folder 100)
  - Griffin, C. E. "Griff" (Box 13, Folder 101)
  - Grinnels, Claude Delbert (Box 13, Folder 102)
  - Gridley, Sidney D. (Box 13, Folder 103)
  - Griffith, Heber Emlyn (Box 13, Folder 104)
  - Griffin, Carroll E. (Box 13, Folder 105)
  - Grubbs, A. Richard "Rich" (Box 13, Folder 106)
  - Hadlock, E. H. (Box 13, Folder 107)
  - Hance, Frances Evaul (Box 13, Folder 108)
  - Hand, Henry Finch (Box 13, Folder 109)
  - Harding, Elias Earl (Box 13, Folder 110)
  - Hantman, Stuart S. (Box 13, Folder 111)
  - Harrington, Charles Mason (Box 13, Folder 112)
  - Hart, Authur J. (Box 13, Folder 113)
  - Havens, William Lewis (Box 13, Folder 114)
  - Haviland, Chilson B. (Box 13, Folder 115)
  - Hawkins, Gene R. (Box 13, Folder 116)
  - Hawley, R. Stephen "Steve" (Box 13, Folder 117)
  - Hayner, Lloyd A. (Box 13, Folder 118)
  - Heath, Riley Henry (Box 13, Folder 119)
  - Heck, Patrick (Box 13, Folder 120)
  - Henderson, Edgar H. (Box 13, Folder 121)
  - Hendy, John J. (Box 13, Folder 122)
  - Hershey, Barclay (Box 13, Folder 123)
  - Herzog, Carl (Box 13, Folder 124)
  - Heuser, Jr., Gustave F. "Gus" (Box 13, Folder 125)
  - Hoard, Lawrence "Larry" (Box 13, Folder 126)
  - Hobart, Alfred L. (Box 13, Folder 127)
  - Hodson, Floyd (Box 13, Folder 128)
  - Holbrook, Elliott M. (Box 13, Folder 129)
  - Holcomb, Donald Marsh "Don" (Box 13, Folder 130)
  - Hoare, John (Box 13, Folder 131)
  - Hollister, Sherman Preston (Box 13, Folder 132)
  - Homan, William (Box 13, Folder 133)
  - Honey, Edwin E. (Box 13, Folder 134)
  - Howard, Lester C. "Let" (Box 13, Folder 135)
  - Hower, D. J. "Dave" (Box 13, Folder 136)
  - Howes, Murray VanCamp (Box 13, Folder 137)
  - Hugo, Francis M. (Box 13, Folder 138)
  - Humphreys, Hugh C. (Box 13, Folder 139)
  - Humphreys, J. Eric (Box 13, Folder 140)
  - Huttar, Jr., John C. "Johnny" (Box 13, Folder 141)
  - Hyde, Tom Bruce (Box 13, Folder 142)
  - Inglis, Burton (Box 13, Folder 143)
  - Ingraham, Arthur E. "Art" (Box 13, Folder 144)
  - James, Wilbur O. (Box 13, Folder 145)
  - Jayne, Allen (Box 13, Folder 146)
  - Jennings, Harry (Box 13, Folder 147)
  - Jessup, George Penny (Box 13, Folder 148)
  - Jette, Morris (Box 13, Folder 149)
  - Johnson, Elmer D. (Box 13, Folder 150)
  - Johnson, Ronald T. "R.T." (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Johnston, Roy Campbell (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Jones, John Paul (Box 13, Folder 153)
  - Jones, Luther G. (Box 13, Folder 154)
  - Jones, Paul Webster (Box 13, Folder 155)
  - Jones, Jr., W. C. (Box 13, Folder 156)
  - Jorsted, Irving C. (Box 13, Folder 157)
  - Kautch, Carl Richard (Box 13, Folder 158)
  - Kennard, Jarman G. "Jerry" (Box 13, Folder 159)
  - Kenworthy, Clarence S. (Box 13, Folder 160)
  - Kern, Clyde Lewis (Box 13, Folder 161)
  - Kessler, Armin George (Box 13, Folder 162)
  - Kezer, Claude Allen (Box 13, Folder 163)
  - Kieth, Arthur Raymond (Box 13, Folder 164)
  - Kimball, Victor G. (Box 13, Folder 165)
  - Kinsman, Daniel F. (Box 13, Folder 166)
  - Kinzey, Bertram York (Box 13, Folder 167)
  - Kirby, Robert Sterns (Box 13, Folder 168)
  - Klesh, David (Box 13, Folder 169)
  - Krakauer, John L. (Box 13, Folder 170)
  - Krauss, William Ernest (Box 13, Folder 171)
  - Kreider, Jerry W. (Box 13, Folder 172)
  - Kuhn, Wayne (Box 13, Folder 173)
  - Ladd, Carl Edwin (Box 13, Folder 174)
  - Lamar, Ralph (Box 13, Folder 175)
  - Larsen, Axel Martin (Box 13, Folder 176)
  - Laube, Herbert David (Box 13, Folder 177)
  - Lewandowski, David M. (Box 13, Folder 178)
  - Lewis, George William (Box 13, Folder 179)
  - Lewis, Herschel P. (Box 13, Folder 180)
  - Lightfoote, Robert "Bob" (Box 13, Folder 181)
  - Little Sisters Communications (Box 13, Folder 182)
  - Livermore, James Northrup (Box 13, Folder 183)
  - Lothers, John E. (Box 13, Folder 184)
  - Lull, R. E. (Box 13, Folder 185)
  - Lutz, John E. (Box 13, Folder 186)
  - Lysle, Richard (Box 13, Folder 187)
  - Mack, Harry Elias (Box 13, Folder 188)
  - Mackert, Edmund M. (Box 13, Folder 189)
  - MacQuigg, D. E. (Box 13, Folder 190)
  - Magnacca, Richard (Box 13, Folder 191)
  - Male, Allen M. (Box 13, Folder 192)
  - Male, John (Box 13, Folder 193)
  - Mallery, John S. (Box 13, Folder 194)
  - Marble, Dean R. (Box 13, Folder 195)
  - Marshall, Henry B. (Box 13, Folder 196)
  - Marx, Walter S. (Box 13, Folder 197)
  - Massey, Louis Milville (Box 13, Folder 198)
  - Oklahoma State Chapter of Acacia (Box 13, Folder 199)
  - Oregon Chapter-Eugene, Oregon (Box 13, Folder 200)
  - Matkin, Paul VanDeren (Box 13, Folder 201)
  - McCann, William I. (Box 13, Folder 202)
  - Mattick, Walter Lester (Box 13, Folder 203)
  - Matusiak, Robert (Box 13, Folder 204)
  - McCartney, John (Box 13, Folder 205)
  - McCuen, John E. (Box 13, Folder 206)
  - McDermott, George Robert (Box 13, Folder 207)
  - McDonald, William F. (Box 13, Folder 208)
  - McMurtry, Richard K. (Box 13, Folder 209)
  - McMaster, Marcus Aurelius (Box 13, Folder 210)
  - McVetty, Percy George (Box 13, Folder 211)
  - Meserve, Wilbur E. (Box 13, Folder 212)
  - Mihalko, Richard Bainer (Box 13, Folder 213)
  - Miller, David J. (Box 13, Folder 214)
  - Miller, Dwight S. (Box 13, Folder 215)
  - Miller, Roy Benson (Box 13, Folder 216)
  - Mills, Wilfred D. (Box 13, Folder 217)
  - Morgan, C. J. "Carlton" (Box 13, Folder 218)
  - Moore, Hollister H. (Box 13, Folder 219)
  - Morris, Fred N. (Box 13, Folder 220)
  - Morrow, Glenn R. (Box 13, Folder 221)
  - Morrow, Lester Wm. (Box 13, Folder 222)
  - Mortimer, Earl J. (Box 13, Folder 223)
  - Mosher, Ted (Box 13, Folder 224)
  - Mueller, George (Box 13, Folder 225)
  - Munsell, Warren A. (Box 13, Folder 226)
  - Munsey, Rodney R. (Box 13, Folder 227)
  - Munson, Arthur Louie (Box 13, Folder 228)
  - Myers, A. E. (Box 13, Folder 229)
  - Myers, Charles Emory (Box 13, Folder 230)
  - Naeter, Albrecht (Box 13, Folder 231)
  - Nash, Jack Thomas (Box 13, Folder 232)
  - Nelson, Jr., Stewart (Box 13, Folder 233)
  - Niven, Charles Franklin (Box 13, Folder 234)
  - Niven, Lola Alenander (Box 13, Folder 235)
  - Nelson, John Herbert (Box 13, Folder 236)
  - Noonburg, William I. (Box 13, Folder 237)
  - Norton, Lytle H. (Box 13, Folder 238)
  - Nuffort, Walter (Box 13, Folder 239)
  - Ochs, Peter C. (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Odegaard, David (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - O'Donnell, William Martin (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Offenberger, Martin (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Ogle, Robert C. (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Onji, Hiroshi (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Overton, Floyd Carter (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Owens, Gary E. (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Paken, John R. (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Palmer, Everett Arthur (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Pasquino, Alan (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Peach, Preston Littlepage (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Peacock, Walter M. (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Pearce, Charles Darius (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Pellow, Frederick L. (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Pendaruis, William (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Petrie, Robert (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Phillips, Lawrence D. (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Pickerill, Horace M. (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Pierce, Howard C. (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Pohl, Chester (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Powell, William R. (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Powers, William H. (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Pratt, Glenn B. (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Preston, John Owings (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Pue, Alan (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Ramey, Blaine Butler (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Rasmason, H. Lewis (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Ramos, George (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Ratsek, J. C. (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Rayburn, Edward B. (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Rayner, Edward E. (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Reed, Harry Clifford (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Rehmeyer, Clyde S. (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Reid, Robert T. (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Repp, Rosive Conkling (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Riley, H. B. (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Richmond, Edward Avery (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Rider, Raymond (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Riebel, David L. (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Rishoi, Alfred Hermann (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Rittershausen, August (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Robb, Byron R. (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Robey, Ashley (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Robie, Merle S. (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Robinson, H. B. (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Robinson, James Ried (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Rogers, Fred Stillman (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Roihl, Norbert (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Roth, Ronald (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Rothenberger, W. H. (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Ruby, George C. (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Rummele, Edward T. (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Rumsey, Lawrence Cooper (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Sanders, Gerald Dewitt (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Sawyer, Samuel Nelson (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Scammell, R. J. (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Schaufler, Ernest E. (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Schellkopf, Sigmund Walter (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Schempp, Jr., G. C. (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Schneider, Birch H. (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Scinta, James (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Searing, Ellis Richard (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Sellers, Oscar W. (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Sharp, Neil F. (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Sheldon, F. David (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Sherk, K. W. (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Shimer, Preston W. (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Showacre, Jim-Personal (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Skidmore, Lauson Bigelow (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Striff, Frederick (Box 14, Folder 71)
  - Skinner, Henry (Box 14, Folder 72)
  - Slocum, Beryl (Box 14, Folder 73)
  - Slocum, Perry D. (Box 14, Folder 74)
  - Smith, Albert Newton (Box 14, Folder 75)
  - Smith, Byron T. (Box 14, Folder 76)
  - Smith, Earl Y. (Box 14, Folder 77)
  - Smith, Sidney Daniel (Box 14, Folder 78)
  - Smith, Russell J. (Box 14, Folder 79)
  - Snider, Robert (Box 14, Folder 80)
  - Soloway, Roger D. (Box 14, Folder 81)
  - Sommers, Thomas W. (Box 14, Folder 82)
  - Sorge, Joseph J. (Box 14, Folder 83)
  - Souter, Charles Edward (Box 14, Folder 84)
  - Spencer, Adrian L. (Box 14, Folder 85)
  - Spencer, Leland (Box 14, Folder 86)
  - Spiesz, Robertson G. (Box 14, Folder 87)
  - Spofford, Harold B. (Box 14, Folder 88)
  - Squires, Robert B. (Box 14, Folder 89)
  - St. Cyr, Beau (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Stagg, Charles Tracey (Box 14, Folder 91)
  - Steelquist, Rubin U. (Box 14, Folder 92)
  - Stewart, Dewey (Box 14, Folder 93)
  - Stewart, Vern B. (Box 14, Folder 94)
  - Stillman, Ron E. (Box 14, Folder 95)
  - Stone, Gerald M. (Box 14, Folder 96)
  - Strahan, James Lewis (Box 14, Folder 97)
  - Stroehlein, Jr., Andrew J. (Box 14, Folder 98)
  - Strong, Everett M. (Box 14, Folder 99)
  - Strong, Howard Herkimer (Box 14, Folder 100)
  - Suiter, Norman Wesley (Box 14, Folder 101)
  - Suiter, Vaughn Douglas (Box 14, Folder 102)
  - Suiter, Wilbur C. (Box 14, Folder 103)
  - Sumner, George Ellsworth (Box 14, Folder 104)
  - Sun, Peter B. (Box 14, Folder 105)
  - Sylvester, William Boyd (Box 14, Folder 106)
  - Symons, James M. (Box 14, Folder 107)
  - Teeter, C. Glenn (Box 14, Folder 108)
  - Teeter, Thomas A. H. (Box 14, Folder 109)
  - Teetsel, Paul K. (Box 14, Folder 110)
  - Tesarik, Ronald E. (Box 14, Folder 111)
  - Tetz, Frank F. (Box 14, Folder 112)
  - Thomas, J. Clyde (Box 14, Folder 113)
  - Thomas, Melven F. (Box 14, Folder 114)
  - Thompson, Milo E. (Box 14, Folder 115)
  - Thompson, Paul Wheeler (Box 14, Folder 116)
  - Tilley, Lloyd Henry (Box 14, Folder 117)
  - Tilley, Norman Nevil (Box 14, Folder 118)
  - Townsend, Marvin (Box 14, Folder 119)
  - Tozier, Hayden H. (Box 14, Folder 120)
  - Tucker, Charles K. (Box 14, Folder 121)
  - Tyler, Leland C. (Box 14, Folder 122)
  - Ulmer, William Ernest (Box 14, Folder 123)
  - Underwood, Francis O. (Box 14, Folder 124)
  - Urban, William P. (Box 14, Folder 125)
  - Urband, Edward Milton (Box 14, Folder 126)
  - Vautrot, Louis R. (Box 14, Folder 127)
  - Vanderhoeff, James Elizah (Box 14, Folder 128)
  - Vickers, Gates S. (Box 14, Folder 129)
  - Vincent, Walter N. (Box 14, Folder 130)
  - Vreeland, Edward Price (Box 14, Folder 131)
  - Wait, J. Paul (Box 14, Folder 132)
  - Walker, Charles L. (Box 14, Folder 133)
  - Walker, Warren (Box 14, Folder 134)
  - Walsh III, John Murray "Jack" (Box 14, Folder 135)
  - Warne, Robert B. (Box 14, Folder 136)
  - Ways, Raymond A. (Box 14, Folder 137)
  - Washbon, Edwin C. (Box 14, Folder 138)
  - Weeden, Samuel A. (Box 14, Folder 139)
  - Wells, Richard J. (Box 14, Folder 140)
  - Westervelt, Earl A. (Box 14, Folder 141)
  - Wetzler, Henry G. (Box 14, Folder 142)
  - Whitson, Donald D. (Box 14, Folder 143)
  - Wickham, Bill (Box 14, Folder 144)
  - Widrig, Francis Smith (Box 14, Folder 145)
  - Wigley, William R. (Box 14, Folder 146)
  - Wilder, Paul (Box 14, Folder 147)
  - Williams, Richard L. (Box 14, Folder 148)
  - Willits, Charles (Box 14, Folder 149)
  - Wilson, John G. (Box 14, Folder 150)
  - Wilson, Leroy A. "Steve" (Box 14, Folder 151)
  - Wing, Stephen R. (Box 14, Folder 152)
  - Wingard, Jr., Lemuel B. "Lem" (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Winkeller, H. B. "Blackie" (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Winters, Rhett Y. (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Wolf, Harold G. (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Wollenweber, Gay (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Wollper, Frederick P. "Gus" (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Wolf, John G. (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Wood, Jeff (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Woodford, Albert (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Young, Park E. (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Correspondence, Marc to Al, 1937 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Additional Acacia Members
    - Barclay, Alexander James
    - Beckman, Carl Theodore
    - Bee, Charles E.
    - Bigelow, Crowel Harry
    - Bizzell, James A
    - Booth, Russell Charles
    - Coffman, Herbert
    - Cole, Dale Stevens
    - Cooper, Herbert Press
    - Daugherty, Edgar Sterling
    - Day, Emmons D.
    - Dolve, Robert Martinus
    - Edsall, Millard J.
    - Ellis, Howard Charles
    - Finch, Ray MacAlpine
    - French, O. L.
    - Gage, Victor Raymond
    - Gillette, Kenneth Gordon
    - Godwin, F. M.
    - Hall, Arthur George
    - Hurd, D. L.
    - Huey, S. J.
    - Jenkins, John Ethbert
    - Johnson, LeRoy E.
    - Jordan, A. E.
    - Lawrence, Leonard A.
    - Loomis, P. L.
    - MacKenzie, E. R.
    - MacQuigg, C. H.
    - Rider, R. L.
- Series XI. Wing Building Documents and Architectural Sketches
  - Acacia Corporation Wing Bills (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Acacia Fraternity General Construction (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Acacia Fraternity Kitchen Equipment (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Acacia Fraternity Specifications for Plumbing Work (Box 14, Folder 167)
  - Acacia Fraternity Electric (Box 14, Folder 168)
  - Color Selection-Acacia Fraternity (Box 14, Folder 169)
  - Transmittals-Acacia Fraternity (Box 14, Folder 170)
  - Certificates of Payments-Acacia (Box 14, Folder 171)
  - Bids-Acacia Fraternity (Box 14, Folder 172)
  - Contracts-Acacia Fraternity (Box 14, Folder 173)
  - Acacia Fraternity 1966 (Box 14, Folder 174)
  - Acacia (Box 14, Folder 175)
  - Acacia Fraternity-Heating and Ventilation (Box 14, Folder 176)
  - House Architectural Records (Box 14, Folder 177)
  - House Architectural Records (Box 14, Folder 178)
  - House Architectural Records (Box 14, Folder 179)
  - 318 Highland Rd. Roof Sketch (Box 14, Folder 180)
  - Showacre '50 Dream House (Box 14, Folder 181)
  - Proposed New Acacia Fraternity House (Box 14, Folder 182)
  - Miscellaneous (Asian Script) (Box 14, Folder 183)
  - Miscellaneous (Asian Script) (Box 14, Folder 184)
- Series XII. Alumni Mailing Cards, #1-854, 1907-1972; The alumni mailing cards were originally housed in green iron drawers designed for the cards. These cards were used until the late 1970s to keep alumni mailing addresses up to date. Generally, they are organized chronologically by initiation date.
  - Alumni Mailing Cards, #1-854, 1907-1972 (Box 15)
  - Alumni directory index card set with charter number (Box 15)
- Series XIII. Architectural Sketches, Blueprints, and Reproductions of Deeds and Other Documents, 1923-2005
  - Sketches and Blueprints (Alterations, Additions, Preliminary Plans, Dream House), 1923-2005 (Box Mss. Collection 44, Folder A)
  - Harriet H. Williams Proposed Apartment Renovations and Acacia Dream House Student Room, Sketch by AJ, 1923 (Box Mss. Collection 44, Folder A)
  - Reproduction of 1923-2005 Sketches and Blueprints (Alterations, Additions, Preliminary Plans, Dream House) (Box Mss. Collection 44, Folder B)
  - Reproduction of Harriet H. Williams Proposed Apartment Renovations and Acacia Dream House Student Room, Sketch by AJ (Box Mss. Collection 44, Folder B)
  - Architectural Design Printing Blocks (3) (Box 17)
  - Reproduction of deeds related to 318 Highland Road (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Reproduction of Constitution and By-Laws, October 1921 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Page from 1909 Cornellian with Acacia Fraternity Crest (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Reproduction of Postcards of Ithaca and Cornell, ca. 1920s (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Series XIV. Ledgers
  - Treasurer's Ledger, 1980-1981 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Activity Ledger, 1990-2004 (Box 18, Folder 2)